<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid19 Tracker 🇮🇳</string>
    <string name="select_state_ut">Select State/UT:</string>
    <string name="type_to_choose_state">Type to Choose State</string>
    <string name="places_with_case">Place with cases:</string>
    <string name="type_to_choose_place">Type to Choose Place</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <!--Notification Channel Strings-->
    <string-array name="notification_channel_name_list">
        <item>Default</item>
        <item>Covid Report</item>
        <item>Covid Rising Nearby</item>
        <item>Buy From Home</item>
        <item>Promotional</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="notification_channel_desc_list">
        <item>Default Notification</item>
        <item>Daily Covid Report</item>
        <item>Alert if covid is rising nearby</item>
        <item>Online purchases of Essentials</item>
        <item>Relevant Promotional Notification</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="notification_channel_id_list">
        <item>default_id</item>
        <item>covid_report_id</item>
        <item>covid_rising_nearby_id</item>
        <item>buy_from_home_id</item>
        <item>promotional_id</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="notification_channel_importance_list">
        <item>3</item><!--IMPORTANCE_DEFAULT-->
        <item>4</item><!--IMPORTANCE_HIGH-->
        <item>5</item><!--IMPORTANCE_MAX-->
        <item>3</item><!--IMPORTANCE_DEFAULT-->
        <item>2</item><!--IMPORTANCE_LOW-->
    </integer-array>

    <string name="covid_report">There is %d new cases in %s, %d new cases in %s and %d new cases in %s. Be safe, be smart, be kind \uD83D\uDE37</string>
    <string name="covid_report_india_only">There is %d new cases in %s. Be safe, be smart, be kind \uD83D\uDE37</string>
    <!--END: Notification Channel Strings-->

    <string name="about_covid19india_title_text">We get our data from <u>covid19india.org</u></string>

    <string name="app_desc_text">
        This app helps you to track Covid19 in indian and it\'s different states and districts.
        This app will give you report daily about covid cases in your nearby area.&lt;br&gt;
        This app will tell you different way to prevent from covid and if unfortunately if you got covid, it will tell you different ways to cure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        The suggestion and guidelines is taken from Health Ministry, Government of India&lt;br&gt;
        There is also a section to buy essential things if required from the comfort of your home.
    </string>

    <string name="share_app_description">Track Covid19 case in the india and stay updated.
        Buy essentials from home. Get Daily Report about covid cases in your area.
         Different ways to prevent and cure covid from official sources of Health Ministry, Government of India
        \n\nDownload %s\n
        https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=%s
    </string>
    <string name="about_covid19india">About covid19india.org</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="indian_map">Indian Map</string>

    <!--About Covid19IndiaOrg Q&A-->
    <string-array name="q_and_a_questions_list">
        <item>Is covid19india.org official?</item>
        <item>What are covid19india.org sources? How is the data gathered for this project?</item>
        <item>Why does covid19india.org have difference in numbers compared to MOHFW website?</item>
        <item>Where can I find the data for this?</item>
        <item>What is covid19india.org?</item>
        <item>Why are covid19india.org guys putting in time and resources to do this while not gaining a single penny from it?</item>
        <item>Is this official app of covid19india.org</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="q_and_a_answers_list">
        <item>No.</item>
        <item>covid19india.org is using state bulletins and official handles to update our numbers.
            The data is validated by a group of volunteers and published into a Google sheet and an API.
            API is available for all at data.covid19india.org.
            We would love it if you can use this data in the fight against this virus. The source list is here(https://telegra.ph/Covid-19-Sources-03-19).</item>
        <item>MoHFW updates the data at a scheduled time. However, covid19india.org updates them based on state press bulletins,
            official (CM, Health M) handles, PBI, Press Trust of India, ANI reports. These are generally more recent.</item>
        <item>All the data is available through an API for further analysis and development here : data.covid19india.org</item>
        <item>covid19india.org are a group of dedicated volunteers who curate and verify the data coming from several sources.
            covid19india.org extracts the details, like a patient\'s relationship with other patients to identify local and community transmissions,
            travel history and status. covid19india.org never collects or expose any personally identifiable data regarding the patients.</item>
        <item>Because it affects all of us. Today it\'s someone else who is getting infected; tomorrow it could be us.
            We need to prevent the spread of this virus.
            We need to document the data so that people with knowledge can use this data to make informed decisions.</item>
        <item>No, this app is only using it\'s api (data.covid19india.org)</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--END About Covid19IndiaOrg Q&A-->
</resources>
